[
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "What is the most hated app in the gamer community?",
    "correct_answer": "TikTok",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Moldova",
      "Czech Republic",
      "Denmark"
    ]
  },
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "What is one of Rick Astleys well known songs?",
    "correct_answer": "Never Gonna Give You Up",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Moldova",
      "Czech Republic",
      "Denmark"
    ]
  },
    {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Who is my daddy?",
    "correct_answer": "Tyler",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Moldova",
      "Czech Republic",
      "Denmark"
    ]
  }, 
      {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "What cube game does everyone in this server play?",
    "correct_answer": "Geometry Dash",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Roblox",
      "Minecraft",
      "Discord"
    ]
  }, 
      {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Who made the void?",
    "correct_answer": "Newo",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Tyler",
      "PigPig",
      "Raging"
    ]
  },
        {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "Who made RoboTop?",
    "correct_answer": "GD Colon",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Tyler",
      "PigPig",
      "Raging"
    ]
  },
          {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "What app am I (AutoBot) hosted on?",
    "correct_answer": "Glitch",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Tyler",
      "PigPig",
      "Raging"
    ]
  }, 
            {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "This server was founded in 2016.",
    "correct_answer": "False",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Tyler",
      "PigPig",
      "Raging"
    ]
  },
              {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "I am the best bot in the server.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Tyler",
      "PigPig",
      "Raging"
    ]
  },
             {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "Discords alpha name was 'Chatcord'",
    "correct_answer": "False",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Tyler",
      "PigPig",
      "Raging"
    ]
  },
               {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "All the underaged people were banned and it took months for one hero to convince the owner to unban them.",
    "correct_answer": "True",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Tyler",
      "PigPig",
      "Raging"
    ]
  },
                 {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
    "question": "What language am I coded in?",
    "correct_answer": "Javascript",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Tyler",
      "PigPig",
      "Raging"
    ]
  },
                   {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "What is the most misunderstood dog breed?",
    "correct_answer": "Walter",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Tyler",
      "PigPig",
      "Raging"
    ]
  },
                     {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
    "question": "What famous singer passed away on 12/8/2019?",
    "correct_answer": "Juice WRLD",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Tyler",
      "PigPig",
      "Raging"
    ]
  },
                       {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
    "question": "Who is the oldest rapper in the world?",
    "correct_answer": "Ice-T",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Tyler",
      "PigPig",
      "Raging"
    ]
  },
                         {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "hard",
      "question": "Find the missing part: .... Barrymore.",
    "correct_answer": "Drew",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Tyler",
      "PigPig",
      "Raging"
    ]
  },        
  {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Who is the richest person in the world?",
    "correct_answer": "PigPig",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Tyler",
      "PigPig",
      "Raging"
    ]
  },
    {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Who was the first person on the moon?",
    "correct_answer": "Hitler",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Drew Barrymore",
      "PigPig",
      "Raging"
    ]
  },
      {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What year did World War II start in?",
    "correct_answer": "1939",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "1989",
      "1947",
      "1950"
    ]
  },
      {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "type": "multiple",
    "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "Find the missing part: ...... Belfort",
    "correct_answer": "Jordan",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Drew Barrymore",
      "PigPig",
      "Raging"
    ]
  },      {
    "category": "General Knowledge",
    "type": "boolean",
    "difficulty": "easy",
      "question": "ur mom",
    "correct_answer": "ewbhfgivfuhufhhffuofg",
    "incorrect_answers": [
      "Drew Barrymore",
      "PigPig",
      "Raging"
    ]
  }
]